# Ha Gia Bao

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

Mobile No.	E-mail.	in LinkedIn.	🕫 Behance.
		in/baronha	baronha

# **SUMMARY**

I am a Front End Developer who are keen on UI/UX, infatuated with beauty, and minimalism. I had over a year of experience in developing mobile applications which based on React Native framework, with knowledge of a user interface designer and insight ears, I totally hope to give to users a great experience inside my product.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

# **Programming Languages:**

- Javascript.

#### **Version Control:**

- Git.

### **Database Management Systems:**

- Firebase
- MS SQL Server

#### Other:

- Good at UI/UX Design.
- Good presentation capabilities.

# Frameworks/ Platforms:

- ReactJS, React Native.
- ES6.
- WebAPI.
- Twitter Bootstrap.

#### **Tools:**

- Visual Studio Code, Xcode.
- Figma, Adobe Illustrator.
- Postman.

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# TTS SERVICES JSC | MAY 2019 - PRESENT

MOBILE DEVELOPER - UI/UX DESIGNER - VISUAL DESIGNER

**Project**: ThiTruongSi E-Commerce Mobile Application (2 members).

- **Description**: ThiTruongSi is a modern model which assists the connection between buyers and wholesalers with each other easily.
- Technologies: React Native, React-Redux, ES6, Axios, Gitlab.
- · Main Responsibilities:
  - Designing UI/UX for Buyer's Mobile Application.
  - Developing modules of the application.
  - Contributing ideas for the future features development.

#### **INNVI LAB | SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019**

FREELANCE DESIGNER

**Project**: D!FF Mobile Application (4 members).

- **Description**: D!FF is a mobile application used to merge the two images together and distinguish the differences between them
- · Tools: Figma, Adobe Illustrator.
- Main Responsibilities:
  - Designing UI/UX for Mobile Application.
  - Designing landing page.
  - Designing Logo.

Project: Số Lạ (4 members).

- **Description**: Số Lạ is a mobile application used to detect spam phone numbers and promptly notify users.
- · Tools: Figma, Adobe Illustrator.
- Main Responsibilities:
  - Designing UI/UX for Mobile Application.

# **EDUCATION**

#### THU DAU MOT UNIVERSITY | MAY 2016 - AUGUST 2020

Major: Software Engineering

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

### PETTY | MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- Description: Petty is an application that connects pet owners and pet adopters.
- Role: Full-stack Developer.
- Technologies: React Native, Firebase, JavaScript, Gitlab.

#### **SMART SWITCH | SEPTEMBER 2019 - OCTOBER 2019**

- **Description**: Smart Switch is a mobile application used turn on/off the light.
- Role: Mobile Developer.
- Technologies: React Native, Firebase, Arduino, JavaScript, Gitlab.

# **T-STUDENTS | AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT**

- **Description**: T-Student is a mobile application used to support student Thu Dau Mot University to participate in extracurricular activities.
- Role: UI/UX Designer, Visual Designer, Front End Developer.
- Technologies: React Native, JavaScript, Gitlab.

# **PASTIMES AND ACTIVITIES**

- · I am interested in reading IT blogs, Medium in my free time and I am also excited with UI/UX Design, It takes me time to refer to the designs on Dribbble and Behance.
- · My other hobbies is photography. I love capturing beautiful landscapes and posting them on my Instagram and personal VSCO account.